Let's start off by talking about work and studies. Currently I just graduated, so I'm in between things. But yeah, I am finding work at this point. Ideally in Mumbai. I'm really interested in like, the startup industry, there are some startups that I'm looking to work with as of— in the moment, right now. So that's just what, like, this next chapter holds for me. Good question. I really feel strongly about philanthropy and education specifically, so I imagine myself living in between, like, different places in India. Pursuing this, like, philanthropic educational work, yeah. So many things. You know, it's kind of like, I don't know, I couldn't choose. I think every day was something different. I would watch, like, a really fun TV show and, for example, Suits and be like, “Oh, I'm going to be a lawyer.” And I was convinced. And then I would watch a really fun movie like Devil Wears Prada and... I wanted to be a fashion designer. So it was many different things when I was younger. Now let's talk about reading. So I don't know if it’s necessarily my favorite, but there is this book called The Secret Garden that I remember reading in my class in the fourth grade, and I'm categorizing it as my favorite book because it just meant a lot to me, because there were really nice descriptions about like, the scenery, and that really got me into reading. So I think for the heartwarming purpose, it's definitely my favorite book when I was younger, but it's just the book that started my love for reading in general. I did a lot of reading. Too much reading. I did a lot of reading that was more literary works and it made me realize, “Oh, I don't like it.” I don't like them. I'm also not a fan of novels, but what I am a fan of is more fiction or self-help kind of books, especially that I'm getting older and I want to incorporate habits into my life. There's this book I read called Daisy Jones & the Six and it was just a really fun book. It was the book I read recently, and I think people who are into fiction and like, music, would really love that book. It was adapted into a series after, so definitely recommend that one. Now let's talk about drinks Okay, there's so many options. Particularly in my family, we have a weird mix of things, but in my country we usually have, like, masala chai, or we have normal sodas, but we put some masala in it, which is like some spice to kind of give it that extra like kick. So that's really common. But in my family we put like, for example, Coke, we put a little bit of vanilla ice cream. And I think it also has to do with like, different places in India also have this. But in my family it's staple. Yeah. Yes, I do. And it's because when I don’t, I can feel the like, adverse effects immediately. So I make sure I drink water every single day. But it's so hard because like, in the hurry of everything, you just forget. Okay, so I have phases in my life. Like, sometimes coffee just tastes too good, but I'm really caffeine sensitive. I've realized this after having very, like, jittery episodes, so if I have coffee, it's a decaf. But I really love tea for, like, different purposes. So like, camomile before sleeping or green tea to detox. Definitely tea. I think it's also like, culturally, like, we are more accustomed to being like, “Can I get you some tea?” So, definitely tea. But also like, coffee is always available if you want. But it’s a special request. Now let's talk about the weekend. So I think it depends on how the week has gone. If it’s a good week, you know, weekend can go any which way. But I think a very crucial point, or part of my routine is like, cold plunging or sauna. I really try and prioritize that because it helps like, my anxiety fade away. I really love exercising, that's a crucial part as well. And just meeting friends and family, I think I carve out time specifically for that because the weekdays can get so busy. Very often. Like, most mornings are like, they begin very lazily. And when it comes to lazy weekends, I don't really thrive on lazy weekends because then I kind of fall into like, a rut. So I try to be lazy enough but not too lazy. I definitely think so. I think that the more I'm using a lot of energy during the week, and maybe doing tasks that don't give me energy that are more draining, I will need time to recuperate, like, during the weekends. So, the more I’m a little bit forced to do things I’m not... Particularly happy about, I think, the more lazy weekends I need. The last time I had to do something in a hurry was quite recently. I think around a month ago I moved out of where I was living and it was in a different country. So what that meant is I had to pack my whole life into two suitcases, since I was moving back home, and... The reason it was all left to the last minute was because I had just went on a trip with my boyfriend to Mexico. So I had around a week once I came back from that trip to pack up everything, to arrange where all my mattresses would go, where my couch would go, and get rid of everything. And it was quite an anxiety inducing experience for me, because I'm a very, like, organized person, even though this doesn't seem like it, but I really am. And so when I had to kind of gather everything, it felt very last minute, even though I had a week and I think till the last hour I had to leave, like, to go to the airport, I was packing things up, but thankfully I had a really— a really good group of friends that were with me blasting music, helping me pack, made it like a really fun, enjoyable experience, and I think that really helped also get some momentum to pack. Otherwise I was feeling really lazy about it. And I think, even after I left, I left some things behind. But my friends went back to my apartment, helped me get rid of it, so... It was definitely a team effort. It takes a village. We've been discussing an occasion when you had to do something in a hurry, and we're going to talk about time management, arriving late, managing time, things like that. Thought about this question a lot because I feel like I've been victim to this situation a lot of the times. I think it depends on how much it happens with the same person. But I think there's obviously some unforeseen circumstances that can arise. I would say that if you can avoid it, because time is really limited and you want to kind of extend respect to your friend. Show them, you know, “I care about your time.” So it's always best to— I personally think, try and arrive on time. Again, it kind of... What I said before, bleeds into this answer a little bit, because I think it’s depending on how recurring is your situation. If there's a certain circumstance that happens every morning, maybe, you know, you're a parent that has to take care of your child, then I think the company should allow for this situation to happen and not give such extreme consequences. I think they should be more accepting and understanding. But I think if it's just because, you know, you've been waking up late for companies... Even though I would, personally, I would be like “it's okay.” I think, you know, time is money, especially nowadays, in like, this corporate capitalistic world. So unfortunately, it makes sense for companies to reprimand. But I would say, not too much. Now let's talk about managing study time. I would say shorter chunks. I'm also saying this understanding the era we are in now where short form media has also influenced, like, how we consume information and what works best for us. So I think more than “what should people do?” It's what I feel would be most productive for them. And I think that maybe like, having little breaks in between can be like kind of motivation. “Okay, let me finish this chapter and then I'll have like a chocolate.” So I think that would be really good. I think so. I recently went to this, like, virtual VR experience where I was learning about the Titanic by, like, a VR headset and this... So I found it like a really fun experience. It was date night for me, but I learned so much. And my first thought after that experience was “I can have fun and learn.” And I felt like my mom, being like, “You can have fun and learn.” But I think that they both can go hand-in-hand, especially nowadays, because there's so many different things available for you to really expand how you consume information. So yeah, I think so. Well done. That’s the end of Part three and the end of the speaking test. Oh, perfect. How did you feel about that? So nice. I love it. Yeah, I think there was no problem for you. Thank you. As you probably heard, that was a very high level response. What I've done is I’ve put her whole transcript into a PDF for you, and I've highlighted all the great expressions, idiomatic language, grammar structures, vocabulary for you, so you can learn from those very high level answers. If you want that, all you have to do is just go to the description or the first pinned comment and you can download that for free today. If you want to watch another IELTS speaking video click here. If you want help with your IELTS Speaking test and you want some tips, click here.